Finding Aid for the Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings, circa 1966-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings, circa 1966-1993
Mus. Arc. 2.2
Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987
6 boxes ( 87 audio recordings ( 52 reel to reel tapes, 35 cassettes ) ( 97 compact discs )) ( 5 linear feet )
The contents were digitally reformatted. The preservation files were created as WAV files at 96kHZ/24bit resolution. The service copies exist as CD audio files and as WAV files at 44kHZ/24bit resolution.
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
The Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings contains 52 reel to reel tapes and 35 cassette recordings, including performances of 38 compositions by Morton Feldman. The collection also includes some events, including the conversations between John Cage and Feldman recorded in 1966 as Radio Happenings I and II, the memorial service for Feldman at St. Mark's Church in New York City, a tribute radio program broadcast by WNYC 7 November 1987 in New York City, and an interview of Jan Williams by Sebastian Claren about Feldman. Other composers represented by recordings include Harrison Birtwistle, Pierre Boulez, John Cage, Barbara Monk Feldman, and Bunita Marcus.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Barbara Monk Feldman.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The original recordings were made on reel-to-reel tapes and cassettes. The contents were digitized in 2013 onto a hard drive with service copies on CDs. Preservation wav files that match the original reel faces are named with roots that match the tape numbering. For example preservation files for the first tape are named ubmu0002_2_01.wav. The CD audio tracks match the contents of the original sources, one track per musical work. Wav files were created from the CD audio and are named using the work numbers listed in the container list with the addition of the suffix "sc" for service copy. Preservation and service audio files are stored in the Institutional Repository.
Biographical Note
Composer Morton Feldman (1926-1987) was best known for his association with the New York School of experimentalist musicians, including composers John Cage, Christian Wolff, and Earle Brown, and pianist David Tudor. In addition to composing approximately 150 works, Feldman also wrote more than three dozen articles about various aspects of music and art.
Feldman was a member of the music department faculty at the State University of New York at Buffalo from 1972-1987. During those years he served as Slee Professor of Music 1972-1973, Edgar Varèse Professor 1975-1987, and Director of the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts, 1976-1980. He was also responsible for creating the June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music in 1975.
Scope and Content Note
The Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings contains 52 reel to reel tapes and 35 cassette recordings that were in Feldman's personal collection. They contain performances of 38 compositions by Morton Feldman. Most of the recordings have never been issued commercially. The collection also includes some events, including the conversations between John Cage and Feldman recorded in 1966 as Radio Happenings I and II, the memorial service for Feldman at St. Mark's Church in New York City, a tribute radio program broadcast by WNYC 7 November 1987 in New York City, and an interview of Jan Williams by Sebastian Claren about Feldman. Other composers represented by recordings include Harrison Birtwistle, Pierre Boulez, John Cage, Barbara Monk Feldman, and Bunita Marcus.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in two series:
I. Reel to reel tapes
II. Cassette tapes
Container List
- Reel to reel tapes, circa 1966-1993, I.; Tape 1-52
  Arranged in three subseries:
  I.A. Reel to reel tapes of compositions by Morton Feldman
  I.B. Reel to reel tapes of events with Morton Feldman
  I.C. Reel to reel tapes of compositions by other composers
  - Reel to reel tapes of compositions by Morton Feldman, circa 1965-1981, I.A; Tape 1-40
    Arranged alphabetically by the title of the first Feldman work on the tape.
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings, Tape 1, 25 January 1974, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; tail out; Location of performance: Boston (Mass.) Second of two tapes containing the entire concert. First tape is Tape 50, containing works by Boulez, Stravinsky, and Knussen. Includes spoken word introductions to each work by announcer William Pierce and conductor Tilson Thomas. (Box 01, Item 01)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_01_01
      Feldman, Morton
      Cello and orchestra
      Performers: Jules Eskin, cello; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Michael Tilson Thomas, conductor
      Duration: 24:50
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_01_02
      Reich, Steve
      Music for mallet instruments, voices, and organ
      Performers: Boston Symphony Orchestra; Michael Tilson Thomas, organ and conductor; Joan Heller, Pamela Fraley, Patricia Miller, voices
      Duration: 21:15
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings, Tape 2, 2 August 1967, 1 5 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; mono; tail out; Location of performances: Unknown Container marked "New version" (Box 01, Item 02)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_02_01
      Chorus and instruments, no. 1
      Performers: Unidentified
      Duration: 5:17
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_02_02
      Christian Wolff in Cambridge
      Duration: 3:52
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings, Tape 3, undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown Divided into two files. (Box 01, Item 03)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_03_01
      Crippled symmetry
      Duration: 89:27
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 4, undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; stereo; Location of performance: Unknown Performers: Unidentified (Box 01, Item 04)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_04_01
      Elemental procedures
      Duration: 18:55
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 5, undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; 2 track stereo; tail out; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown (Box 01, Item 05)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_05_01
      False relationships and the extended ending
      Duration: 18:21
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 6, undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown Marked and crossed out on original container: "Piano (1977) Roger Woodward - piano, Baden Baden 1977" (Box 01, Item 06)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_06_01
      Flute and orchestra
      Duration: 34:44
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 7-11, undated, 5 10 inch reels; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown Divided into five files. (Box 01, Item 07-11)
      Work numbers: ubmu0002_2_07_01--ubmu0002_2_11_01
      For Christian Wolff
      Duration: 3:23:18
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 12, February 1974, 1 5 inch reel; Performers: Office de Radiodiffusion-Télévision Française Location of performance: Paris (France)? (Box 01, Item 12)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_12_01
      For Frank O'Hara
      Duration: 18:00
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 13, undated, 1 7 inch reel; Duration of entire tape: 44 minutes Performers: Creative Associates? Location of performance: Buffalo (New York) All three pieces done on Evenings for New Music, but different programs (Box 01, Item 13)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_13_01
      Duration: 21:36
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_13_02
      Moran, Robert
      L'apres-midi du Dracoula
      Duration: 12:36
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_13_03
      Scherchen, Tona
      Tzoue
      Duration: 10:07
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 14-15, 13 March 1982, 2 7 inch reels; Performers: Paul Zukofsky, violin; Aki Takahashi, piano Location of performance: Symphony Space (New York, N.Y.) Marked Part I and II (Box 02, Item 14-15)
      Work numbers: ubmu0002_2_14_01--ubmu0002_2_15_01
      For John Cage
      Duration: 1:04:15
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 16, January 1975, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; stereo; Performers: S.E.M. Ensemble Location of performance: Unknown "Studio Recording"; Piece Commissioned by S.E.M. Ensemble (Box 02, Item 16)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_16_01
      Instruments, no. 1
      Duration: 22:08
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 17, 27 October 1981, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; 1/4 track stereo; Performers: Bowery Ensemble Location of performance: Unknown Recording has a pronounced audio hum. Musical work followed by 16 minutes of ambient sound. (Box 02, Item 17)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_17_01
      Duration: 19:36
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 18, undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; stereo; ½ track; Contents from label on front which states "BBC". Handwritten contents on back of container not Feldman works. (Box 02, Item 18)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_18_01
      Performers: Creative Associates
      Duration: 26:25
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_18_02
      Voice and Instruments 2
      Performers: Matrix: Jane Manning, soprano; Francis Christou, clarinet; Jennifer Ward Clarke, cello; Robin McGee, double bass
      Duration: 11:44
      Recorded from BBC Music in our time broadcast 9 December 1975.
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 19, 4 June 1976, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; 2 track stereo; tail out; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown (Box 02, Item 19)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_19_01
      Instruments, no. 2
      Duration: 20:23
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 20, undated, 1 5 3/4 inch reel; Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Han de Vries, oboe; Jan Williams, percussion Location of performance: Cologne (Germany)? "W.D.R." (Westdeutscher Rundfunk) (Box 02, Item 20)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_20_01
      Instruments, no. 3
      Duration: 22:29
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 21, 13 July, no year, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; stereo; ½ track; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown (Box 02, Item 21)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_21_01
      Madame Press died last week at ninety
      Duration: 4:55
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 22, 16 March 1972, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; stereo; tail out; Location of performance: London (England) "BBC Invitation Concert Part II, Broadcasting House" Each work preceded and followed by commentary. (Box 02, Item 22)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_22_01
      Performers: Fires of London (Michael Laird, trumpet, Roger Brenner, trombone, Avera Williams, flute, John Pigneguy, horn, Martin Fry, tuba, John Steer, Rodney Slatford, bass, Madeline Sampson, violoncello); Peter Maxwell Davies, conductor
      Duration: 7:28
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_22_02
      Three clarinets, cello and piano
      Performers: Matrix: Francis Christou, Alan Hacker, Tony Coe, clarinets; Jennifer Ward Clarke, cello; Paul Crossley, piano
      Duration: 12:42
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_22_03
      I met Heine on the Rue Fürstenburg
      Performers: Mary Thomas, voice; Fires of London; Peter Maxwell Davies, conductor
      Duration: 14:21
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_22_04
      Piano three hands
      Duration: 7:24
      Performers: Morton Feldman and Harrison Birtwistle, piano
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 23, 2 June 1976, 1 5 3/4 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; stereo; Performers: Han de Vries, oboe; Hilversum Radio Philharmonic Orchestra; Jean Fournet, conductor Location of performance: Rotterdam, Netherlands Followed by announcement of personnel (Box 02, Item 23)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_23_01
      Oboe and orchestra
      Duration: 17:39
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 24, 18 September 1976, 1 5 3/4 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; NAB stereo; Performers: Scottish National Orchestra; Elgar Howarth, conductor Location of performance: Bute Hall, Glasgow University World premiere performance Preceded and followed by announcer's introduction (Box 02, Item 24)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_24_01
      Orchestra
      Duration: 20:32
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 25, undated, 1 5 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; mono; fulltrack; Performers: New York Philharmonic; Leonard Bernstein, conductor Location of performance: New York (N.Y.) The back of the container also lists Swallows of Salangan but it is not on the tape. Probably the performance by New York Philharmonic originally on Columbia Records, 1965. (Box 02, Item 25)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_25_01
      Out of "Last pieces"
      Duration: 10:47
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 26, undated, 1 5 inch reel; Tail out; Location of performance: Unknown Swallows of Salangan crossed out on back of container but it is on the tape. The performance is preceded by an announcement in French. (Box 02, Item 26)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_26_01
      Duration: 10:58
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_26_02
      Swallows of Salangan
      Performers: Unidentified but possibly Henri Pousseur, conductor
      Duration: 5:47
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 27, undated, 1 5 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; mono; Location of performance: Unknown Box is marked "Do not open - has to be spliced" (Box 02, Item 27)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_27_01
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_27_02
      Duration: 4:57
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 28, undated, 1 7 inch reel; tail out; Performers: Roger Woodward, piano Location of performance: Unknown Marked "R.W. Piano" Preceded by one minute of unidentified content. (Box 03, Item 28)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_28_01
      Piano (1977)
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 29, 10 November 1980, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; tail out; Performers: Aki Takahashi Location of performance: Buffalo (New York) (Box 03, Item 29)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_29_01
      Duration: 31:28
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 30 28 August 1980, 1 7 inch reel; 3 3/4 ips; NAB stereo; 2 tracks; Location of performance: Edinburgh (Scotland) First U.K. performances of both pieces. (Box 03, Item 30)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_30_spoken_01
      Conversation with composer Morton Feldman, pianist Roger Woodward, and cellist Christopher Gough
      Duration: 7:50
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_30_01
      Piano and orchestra
      Performers: Roger Woodward, piano; BBC Scottish Symphony Orchestra; Henry Lewis, conductor
      Duration: 22:52
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_30_02
      String quartet and orchestra
      Performers: Edinburgh String Quartet; BBC Scottish Symphony Orchestra; Henry Lewis, conductor
      Duration: 30:14
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 31, 28 August 1980, 1 10 inch reel; Location of performance: Edinburgh (Scotland) Copy of reel 30. There was a previous unexplained note about this being unplayable. (Box 03, Item 31)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_31_spoken_01
      Duration: 7:51
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_31_01
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_31_02
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 32, 4 February 1967, 1 7 inch reel; Performers: Neely Bruce, Dennis Kam, Morton Feldman, pianos Location of performance: University of Illinois Festival of Contemporary Arts (Box 03, Item 32)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_32_01
      Pieces, piano (3)
      Duration: 14:34
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 33, 1976?, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; stereo; ½ track; Performers: Gregg Smith Singers, Gregg Smith, conductor Location of performance: Columbia Studios, New York or London "from AL 34138" (issued on Odyssey) Audible click from turntable needle on LP (Box 03, Item 33)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_33_01
      Rothko Chapel
      Duration: 26:21
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 34, undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; stereo; ½ track; Performers: Unidentified, probably Gregg Smith Singers Location of performance: Unknown "copy of job 86665" - a copy of Tape 33 with Gregg Smith Singers (Box 03, Item 34)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_34_01
      Duration: 25:37
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 35, 2 June 1978, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; 2 tracks; Performers: Paul Zukofsky, violin; Ursula Oppens, piano Location of performance: Unknown (Box 03, Item 35)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_35_01
      Spring of Chosroes
      Duration: 20:28
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 36, 3 June 1980, 1 10 inch reel; Performers: Benjamin Hudson, Carol Zeavin, violins; Janet Lyman Hill, viola; Andre Emelianoff, violoncello Location of performance: Buffalo Only date supplied on box. Must be June in Buffalo performance. Defective audio (Box 03, Item 36)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_36_01
      Quartets, strings, no. 1
      Duration: 1:43:37
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 37, undated, 1 5 inch reel; Performers: Unidentified Label on original container states Swallows of Salangan, Sveriges Radio, Stockholm '65 (or '68), Kagel. (Box 03, Item 37)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_37_01
      Unidentified orchestral work not by Feldman
      Duration: 5:58
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 38, 1965?, 1 5 inch reel; Performers: Mauricio Kagel, conductor? Location of performance: Stockholm (Box 03, Item 38)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_38_01
      Duration: 6:25
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 39, undated, 1 7 inch reel; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown (Box 04, Item 39)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_39_01
      Turfan fragments
      Duration: 29:54
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 40, September 1971, 1 5 3/4 inch reel; Location of performance: Venice Biennale (for Viola in my life no. 4) (Box 04, Item 40)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_40_01
      Unidentified work for piano, electronics, and percussion
      Duration: 12:05
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_40_spoken_01
      German language instruction, preceded by brief excerpt of a German song
      Duration: 30:21
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_40_02
      Viola in my life IV
      Karen Phillips, viola; Orchestre Philharmonique de l'O.R.T.F.; Marcello Panni, conductor
      Duration
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_40_03
      Duration: 19:30
      Same performance as above
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_40_04
      Duration: 19:58
      Same performance as first work on tape
  - Reel to reel tapes of events with Morton Feldman, 1966, I.B; Tape 41-45
    Arranged in chronological order.
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 41, July 1966, 1 7 inch reel; Performers: John Cage and Morton Feldman in conversation Location of performance: WBAI, New York (New York) (Box 04, Item 41)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_41_01
      Radio happening I part 1
      Duration: 28:25
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 42, July 1966, 1 7 inch reel; Performers: John Cage and Morton Feldman in conversation Location of performance: WBAI, New York (New York) (Box 04, Item 42)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_42_01
      Radio happening I part 2
      Duration: 16:30
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 43, 12 September 1966, 1 7 inch reel; Performers: John Cage and Morton Feldman in conversation Location of performance: WBAI, New York (New York) (Box 04, Item 43)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_43_01
      Radio happening II part 1
      Duration: 29:20
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 44, 12 September 1966, 1 7 inch reel; Performers: John Cage and Morton Feldman in conversation Location of performance: WBAI, New York (New York) (Box 04, Item 44)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_44_01
      Radio happening II part 2
      Duration: 25:26
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 45, 12 September 1966, 1 7 inch reel; Performers: John Cage and Morton Feldman in conversation Location of performance: WBAI, New York (New York) (Box 04, Item 45)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_45_01
      Radio happening II (complete)
      Duration: 55:55
  - Reel to reel tapes of compositions by other composers, 1974-1980, I.C; Tape 46-52
    Arranged alphabetically by composer's surname and then by the title of the first composition on the tape.
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 46, 9 October 1979?, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; NAB stereo; Performers: Ensemble Inter-Contemporaine; John Alldis Choir; Peter Estvös, conductor Location of performance: Royal Albert Hall First U.K. performance. (Box 04, Item 46)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_46_01
      Birtwistle, Harrison
      agm
      Duration: 33:54
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 47, 25-26 January 1974, 1 7 inch reel; Location of performance: Boston (Mass.) First of two tapes containing the entire concert which also included Feldman's Cello and orchestra and Reich's Music for mallet instruments (Tape 1) Spoken introductions by Boston Symphony announcer William Pierce and conductor Michael Tilson Thomas precede each work. (Box 04, Item 47)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_47_01
      Boulez, Pierre
      Eclat
      Performers: Boston Symphony Orchestra; Michael Tilson Thomas, conductor
      Duration: 11:20
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_47_02
      Stravinsky, Igor
      Abraham and Isaac
      Performers: David Evitts, baritone; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Michael Tilson Thomas, conductor
      Duration: 12:25
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_47_03
      Knussen, Oliver
      Symphony no. 3. Introduction and masque
      Duration: 7:10
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 48, 19 December 1980, 1 7 inch reel; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown (Box 04, Item 48)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_48_01
      Cage, John
      Cheap imitation
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 49, undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; ½ track; tail out (Box 04, Item 49)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_49_01
      Marcus, Bunita
      Oboe, clarinet, bass clarinet, trumpet, trombone
      Duration: 18:10
      Performed April 17, 1978
      Location of performance: Buffalo (N.Y.)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_49_02
      Piano piece (1979)
      Duration: 12:58
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 50, 11 April 1978, 1 5 3/4 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; stereo; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown (Box 04, Item 50)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_50_01
      Xenakis, Iannis
      Dmaathen
      Duration: 11:40
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 51, undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown (Box 04, Item 51)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_51_01
      Gmeeoorh
      Duration: 29:19
    - Morton Feldman Collection of Audio Recordings Tape 52, undated, 1 11 cm reel; 7 ½ ips; Performers: Unidentified Location of performance: Unknown (Box 04, Item 52)
      Work number: ubmu0002_2_52_01
      Nuits
      Duration: 9:37
- Cassette tapes, circa 1966-1993, II.; Tape 53-87; All cassettes stored in one flat container.
  I.A. Cassette tapes of compositions by Morton Feldman
  I.B. Cassette tapes of events concerning or with Morton Feldman
  I.C. Cassette tapes of compositions by other composers
  - Cassette tapes of compositions by Morton Feldman, 1967-1987, II.A; Tape 53-71